=Let's Go Fighting= =Episode 28=
= لنبدأ القتال = = الحلقة 28 =
(I've found several patents)
(لقد وجدت عدة براءات اختراع)
(to deal with Mo Feng.)
(للتعامل مع مو فنغ.)
(Take a look.)
(إلق نظرة.)
Mo Chen.
مو تشن.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
Mo Feng wants to fund the project
يريد Mo Feng تمويل المشروع
(Investment Introduction Plan) of the Industrial Park.
(خطة مقدمة الاستثمار) للمجمع الصناعي.
Here it is again.
ها هو مرة أخرى.
He seems to be trying to force you
يبدو أنه يحاول إجبارك
to dilute your shares.
لتخفيف أسهمك.
Are we just going to
هل نحن فقط ذاهبون إلى
watch him get his way?
مشاهدته يحصل في طريقه؟
Can we find evidence
هل يمكننا العثور على دليل
of what Xia Xingrun said?
لما قاله شيا Xingrun؟
What evidence?
ما الدليل؟
(Mu Li,)
(مو لي ،)
let me give you a hint.
دعني أعطيك تلميح.
I have something
لدي شيئ ما
you need in my safe.
تحتاجه في خزنتي.
Whether you can get it
ما إذا كان يمكنك الحصول عليها
depends on your ability.
يعتمد على قدرتك.
Xia Xingrun has a document
شيا Xingrun لديه وثيقة
proving that Mr. D manipulated the market illegally
يثبت أن السيد "د" تلاعب بالسوق بشكل غير قانوني
in the safe.
في الخزنة.
But we
ولكننا
can't find it.
لا يمكن العثور عليه.
Looks like
يشبه
it's time to wrap it up.
حان الوقت لاختتامها.
A rare guest.
ضيف نادر.
What
ماذا او ما
are you doing here?
تفعلين هنا؟
Feng,
فنغ ،
I want to give you
انا اريد ان اعطيك
two options.
خيارين.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Read it first.
اقرأها أولاً.
(The Mu's and the MOHS's Shares) Competition agreement.
اتفاقية المنافسة (أسهم Mu's و MOHS).
Complete the investment attraction of the industrial park?
استكمال جاذبية الاستثمار للمجمع الصناعي؟
Interesting.
مثير للإعجاب.
I just wonder
انى اتسائل فقط
if you dare to compete with me
إذا كنت تجرؤ على التنافس معي
this time.
هذا الوقت.
According to the competition agreement,
وفقًا لاتفاقية المنافسة ،
Mo Feng will definitely
سوف مو فنغ بالتأكيد
use Starwu to fund.
استخدم Starwu في التمويل.
What is this
ما هذا
thing for?
لشيء؟
This is the gen
هذا هو الجنرال
Xia Xingrun gave me.
أعطاني شيا Xingrun.
Xia Xingrun?
شيا Xingrun؟
Why?
لماذا ا؟
OK.
نعم.
I like
انا يعجبني
playing games the most.
أكثر من يلعب الألعاب.
But,
ولكن،
this time,
هذا الوقت،
I wanna bet on something bigger.
أريد أن أراهن على شيء أكبر.
Go ahead.
إنطلق.
Whoever loses the project of the industrial park
كل من خسر مشروع المنطقة الصناعية
will leave the Mu Group.
سيترك فريق Mu.
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
This is Starwu's graphic design.
هذا هو التصميم الجرافيكي لـ Starwu.
His office is here.
مكتبه هنا.
The meeting room is here.
غرفة الاجتماعات هنا.
Mu Li and I
أنا و Mu Li
will go to his office
سيذهب إلى مكتبه
to find the safe.
للعثور على الخزنة.
But Mo Feng
لكن مو فنغ
is always in the company,
دائمًا في الشركة ،
so it is difficult for us to get the document.
لذلك يصعب علينا الحصول على المستند.
What should we do?
ماذا علينا ان نفعل؟
(Xu Weilai: A buyer has been found for Starwu's business.)
(Xu Weilai: تم العثور على مشتر لأعمال Starwu.)
Are you afraid,
هل انت خائف،
Miss Mu?
ملكة جمال مو؟
OK.
نعم.
It's a deal.
انها صفقة.
Then I'll hold Mo Feng off.
ثم سأحمل مو فنغ.
No.
رقم.
It's obviously my job.
من الواضح أنها وظيفتي.
You've been on the news.
كنت في الأخبار.
Just news.
مجرد أخبار.
It's OK.
كل شيء على مايرام.
No.
رقم.
I have to go to ensure
لا بد لي من الذهاب للتأكد
that nothing goes wrong.
أن لا شيء يسير على ما يرام.
I will always be with you.
سأبقى دائما معك.
Later, Lu and Tang Xue
في وقت لاحق ، لو وتانغ شيويه
will find Mo Feng to sign a contract.
سوف تجد Mo Feng لتوقيع عقد.
Pay attention to business points
انتبه إلى نقاط العمل
and don't blow your cover.
ولا تفجير الغطاء الخاص بك.
What about you?
وماذا عنك؟
We will pretend to be electricians
سوف نتظاهر بأننا كهربائيين
to find the agreement.
للعثور على الاتفاق.
You must hold Mo Feng off
يجب أن تمسك Mo Feng بعيدًا
in the meeting room.
في غرفة الاجتماعات.
Eh,
إيه ،
how can we get in?
كيف يمكننا الدخول
Xu Weilai will come to meet us.
سيأتي Xu Weilai لمقابلتنا.
- Xu Weilai?
- Xu Weilai؟ - Xu Weilai؟
This time, when I help Mu Li,
هذه المرة ، عندما أساعد Mu Li ،
he may take the opportunity to hold me down.
قد ينتهز الفرصة ليحبطني.
Boss,
رئيس،
I can do everything for you
بإمكاني فعل أي شيء لأجلك
without hesitation.
بدون تردد.
I want you to sneak up on Mo Feng
أريدك أن تتسلل إلى مو فنغ
to investigate the Starwu.
للتحقيق في Starwu.
Ah.
آه.
Boss,
رئيس،
you let me go to Feng,
سمحت لي بالذهاب إلى فنغ ،
which is too difficult.
وهو أمر صعب للغاية.
It is time to pay your mother's medical bills.
حان الوقت لدفع الفواتير الطبية لوالدتك.
Let's see if he will take the bait.
دعونا نرى ما إذا كان سيأخذ الطعم.
So these
لذلك هؤلاء
are your ideas.
هي أفكارك.
But Xu Weilai
لكن Xu Weilai
is a little clumsy.
قليلا أخرق.
Is he reliable?
هل هو جدير بالثقة؟
Sure!
بالتأكيد!
Go.
يذهب.
Boss,
رئيس،
I was kicked out by Feng.
لقد طردت من قبل فنغ.
(Starwu)
(جاع)
Mr. Mo, right?
السيد مو ، أليس كذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
You are?
أنت؟
Miss Tang, right?
آنسة تانغ ، أليس كذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
This is?
هذا هو؟
He's my bodyguard.
إنه حارسي الشخصي.
I feel like
أنا أحس مثل
I've seen him somewhere.
لقد رأيته في مكان ما.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Eh.
إيه.
He is the bodyguard I hired from abroad.
إنه الحارس الشخصي الذي عينته من الخارج.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Isn't Mr. Mo's project urgent?
أليس مشروع السيد مو عاجلاً؟
Let's talk about the project first.
لنتحدث عن المشروع أولاً.
OK.
نعم.
Let's talk inside.
لنتحدث في الداخل.
Hey,
يا،
what do you do?
ماذا تعمل؟
Hello,
مرحبًا،
we are
نحن
the electricians that Xu Weilai asked
الكهربائيين الذين طلبهم Xu Weilai
to repair the network.
لإصلاح الشبكة.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Then go in.
ثم ادخل.
Wait!
انتظر!
=Let's Go Fighting=
= لنبدأ القتال =
♪The soul falls to the bottom of the lake♪
الروح تسقط في قاع البحيرة
♪Broken stars pierce the sky♪
♪ النجوم المكسورة تخترق السماء ♪
♪Secrets hidden in the cloud♪
♪ أسرار مخبأة في السحابة ♪
♪From the Milky Way♪
♪ من درب التبانة ♪
♪Belong to you♪
ملك لك ♪